Nothing is ever black or white.
The Sunset Limited is a drama, tv movie film directed by Tommy Lee Jones.
A deeply religious black ex-con thwarts the suicide attempt of an asocial white college professor who tries to throw himself in front of an oncoming subway train, 'The
Sunset Limited.' As the one attempts to connect on a rational, spiritual and emotional level, the other remains steadfast in his hard-earned despair.
Locked in a philosophical debate, both passionately defend their
personal credos and try to convert the other.
White, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Black, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
The Sunset Limited is a 2011 American drama television film directed
by Tommy Lee Jones, who also stars with Samuel L.
It was the duo's second collaboration, after the 2000 film Rules of Engagement.
The screenplay was written by Cormac McCarthy, based
on his 2006 play of the same name.
The film is about the relationship between a Christian African American who has a
positive view of life and a nihilistic white man with a very negative view.
The film aired on HBO on February 12, 2011, and
received generally favorable reviews.
The film explores themes of nihilism, faith, optimism, matter
of life and death, based on play or musical.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.